{
    "subject": "resource/Pontiac_Astre",
    "predicate": "ontology/bodyStyle",
    "object": "resource/Hatchback",
    "human_readable": "The body style of Pontiac Astre is Hatchback.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9051556587219238,
            "question": "What is the body style of a Pontiac Astre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6275543570518494,
            "question": "Give an example of another car with a Hatchback body style."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5987691283226013,
            "question": "What are the advantages of a Hatchback body style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5963380336761475,
            "question": "What features made the Pontiac Astre stand out?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.577992856502533,
            "question": "Besides a Hatchback, what other body styles are common for cars?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47265705466270447,
            "question": "What type of car is a Pontiac Astre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4475581645965576,
            "question": "Is a Pontiac Astre a sedan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2632715404033661,
            "question": "How popular were Pontiac Astres during their production years?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24360337853431702,
            "question": "When were Pontiac Astres commonly produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16715699434280396,
            "question": "What other car models from Pontiac are you familiar with?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The body style of Pontiac Astre is Hatchback.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4466_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When were Pontiac Astres commonly produced?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4466_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How popular were Pontiac Astres during their production years?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4466_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is a Pontiac Astre a sedan?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4466_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4466_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4466_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4466_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4466_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4466_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4466_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4466_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4466_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4466_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4466_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** According to the provided context, the Pontiac Astre did indeed offer a hatchback body style. Specifically, it mentions that the Astre was one of the few American subcompact cars at the time to offer a hatchback body style, which gained popularity in Europe."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}